If someone wished to go to
heaven, there may be a way.
Yes, but how does one actually do it?
I must know.
Ah, well, I wrote down
the process in a notebook.
But, before I could access
that book and find out how...
For the next 20 years, I was forced to
wait, to finally obtain Jotaro's memory.
I can read the contents of
the notebook in his disk.
The culprit's goal relies
on their ability to
steal people's stands by
making them materialize.
I don't believe my
father is actually dead.
I think he'll be okay if
I can get his stand back.
I've won.
Don't underestimate me, you insolent brat!
This changes nothing!
Even when Starplanum returned,
your father would be nothing
more than a broken puppet!
And the user still has
my father's memory disk.
Now's the best chance I'm gonna
get to discover who they are!
Using your unique abilities, there
is something I would like to try.
Really?
Does that belong to a human?
Well, whose bone is it?
That is none of your business.
Let's just say it belongs to
a very old friend of mine.
The bone of my dear friend, the Great Dio.
Thank you so much for watching.
We're going to be my own?
Break out, we're coming up!
Now, we're not going to be able to say.
Break out, we're going to be your own.
I'm not going to be my own.
I don't know what you're going to say.
We're going to be right now.
I don't stop beating, don't stop beating.
Don't stop beating a man!
Stone Ocean!
Julie, no!
Is this a stand ability?
If it is, then obviously Palesnake
must have put a disc into him.
So that means...
Yeah, I get it now.
Jolene, please, take FF and
get the hell out of here!
This problem is mine and mine alone!
It's got nothing to do with either of you!
Actually, no, Hermes.
I'm sorry, but this isn't
just your problem anymore.
Sports Maximum must have
some kind of purpose.
And I would bet it has something to
do with my father's stolen memory.
He must be searching for a
very specific thing in here.
Here's what else.
We'll find out what if we read the disc
that's in that scumbag Sports
Maximum's head. Great idea.
Maybe you should think about getting
the fuck out of this hallway first.
Don't even worry about him.
He'll drown in that pipe soon anyway.
Then his stand ability will
be gone along with him.
Something is off here. Huh?
You said there was an invisible
alligator corpse. Where is it?
If it moves, I should be able
to locate it through my thread.
It's the wall!
What?!
We're screwed.
To that invisible
corpse, ceiling or floor,
front wall or back wall,
it's got us from any angle!
Leave her alone!
It's me you want!
I'm your enemy!
Not true, Hermes.
You two aren't the only
ones in this fight.
That bastard ate half of my leg
like it was some afternoon snack.
I wonder if it's still inside its stomach.
You bet your ass it's my enemy, too!
No, FF! Don't do that!
We still don't know where it's hiding!
It'll bite you again!
Stop!
You'll only make it worse!
You're right.
It will bite me.
That's all it knows how to do,
its whole reason for being.
But see, it's all good now.
I've reached inside his filthy mouth!
Hell yeah.
I actually managed to pull it off.
Totally took that thing out!
Look at this.
I think it's part of
your shoulder, Jolene.
Aw, damn it.
I'm not even sure that fits.
It's been chopped into a ton of pieces.
Here, FF, you need this. Thanks.
I definitely do.
Oh! Hang on. One sec.
Huh?
Hermes.
Tell me something.
Was that creature that attacked and tried
to kill us actually an alligator ghost?
And was it also being controlled
by Sports Maximum? Uh-uh.
I don't think so.
It's too insane.
Remember, not a ghost, but
an invisible corpse. Huh?
The living dead whose primary
instinct is hunting for blood,
but his terrible power is
creating invisible zombies.
Huh?
Shit, not good.
What's wrong, Hermes?
What happened to Sports Maximum?
Did he finally drown down there?
It's too dark, so I can't be sure.
Maybe he's stuck deeper down in the pipe?
Or...
These sure as shit look like handprints!
Damn, that was too close.
The back of my throat is
all wet, gooey, and sticky.
I need to gargle, like now.
Why can't I remember what I was doing
before, and which way was I trying to go?
Oh, right.
I remember now.
It was to the chapel.
I'm going to the chapel.
And my objective, once I'm there,
is to find and take that bone.
Make sure you understand this clearly.
If you fail me, I'll be taking
back the ability I gave you,
and I won't be gentle about it.
That's good.
My power, Limp Bizkit, can
get the job done, and it will.
When I possess the bone that
pale snake ordered me to find,
I'll be able to.
Wait, damn it.
I really need to take a rest
before I do anything else.
I want to wash this grime off my body
and pour something down my throat.
A fresh, cleansing, and
refreshing beverage.
Oh?
That woman over there.
Good timing.
The skanky, um, what was her name again?
I forgot it.
Bitch will do fine.
The bribe was in my hand, but
he won't even acknowledge me.
Hey, how you doing tonight?
Are you on duty, so to speak?
I need to go get a drink right now.
Feel like coming to the cafe with me.
Then we can find a nice
dark corner somewhere
and have ourselves a
little old-fashioned fun.
How about it, huh?
What do you say to wiping
each other's bodies down?
Hey, asshole!
Don't put your fucking
hands on me unless I say so!
You want to handle the merchandise?
Show me the money first!
I wasn't trying to do anything, lady.
Did this slimy little bottom dweller just
attempt to touch you and
not even offer to pay?
Shit!
Where does Sports Maximum go?
We gotta find him!
Maybe when that zombie-ass
alligator was trying to kill us,
he wormed his way out of the pipe.
Or maybe he somehow transformed
into an invisible corpse himself!
I just kicked you a little bit.
Don't be an idiot and you won't get hurt.
What do you mean, be an idiot?
You have to earn their
respect or it's all over.
You must make them pay
or there's no point.
Why don't you help me look, too?
Did you hear me?
Come on find his money.
Oh There's a telling
bulge in his sleeve, huh?
You're kidding me.
So you had the cash the whole time.
Why didn't you say so before jerk?
I literally just told you that
you really are slow aren't you I?
Wonder if he's hiding anything
else somewhere in this husk.
Maybe I could find it in here
What the hell so you want me to really
right here with you yeah i don't even
want to try to figure this out oh no
way i have seen enough this is so not
happening i have done some weird shit
but this is way off the charts huh hope
you don't mind i'll be taking this
what an excellent find thank Thank you.
Wait, what the hell is this?
It's for sure not drugs.
It's oozing from under my skin.
It reeks just like shit.
It's raw sewage.
Oh no, it's everywhere.
I have actual shit seeping from
every single orifice in my body.
Son of a...
Does this mean I actually...
Holy crap, what's happening?
That is shit!
Coming right out of the air!
It's not that I was so
desperate for a drink.
I was truly starving.
The only way I could quench this
thirst was by eating brains.
It's not my fault.
Oh, I remember now.
I had already died by drowning
in that putrid pipe back there.
That bitch.
It's all her fault.
Gloria Costello's despicable sister.
How dare she do that to me?
She'll pay for it.
Seriously, how dare she?
I'M SO THIRSTY!
Hermes! Look!
Keep your eyes open.
I knew that bastard got out of the pipe.
What did he do to that poor girl?
Did...
did he bite her?
What's happening?
She's just a pile of bloody flesh.
Can human teeth really
do that much damage?
He's clearly not human
anymore, in mind or morals.
But I'd be willing to bet he must
have his discs on him right now.
Excellent.
I'm gonna go get them from him then.
So, Jolene, I want you to go wait outside.
Shit! He got away!
Stay close to me, Hermes!
We've been trapped inside!
He has intelligence, like a human!
And keep your distance from the walls.
We already went through that shitshow.
They're not constrained to the floor I'll
track his location in the third dimension.
Found you bitch!
Hanging from the ceiling real clever then
you must have had a bone broken, huh?
Even with a broken arm right I
forgot he's just a rotting corpse now
Go Notion!
I got him!
No!
Jolene, wait!
That isn't Sports Maxima under there!
He was moving the dead girl's corpse
as a decoy, and you bought it!
Jolene, no!
Jolene!
Where is he?
Come on out, motherfucker!
Are you okay?
Hey, Jolene, stop moving and stay point!
This is not your battle
to fight, you know.
Sports Maximum is my problem, not yours!
Hermes, I told you
before, we've leveled up.
This goes way beyond just revenge, or what
you consider your own personal problem.
What?
And it's not even just that.
We don't have the time or
the room to even think.
Do you understand that?
Now look.
No, it can't be.
Oh, yes, it can.
We didn't catch it then, but he already
backed us into a corner a long time ago.
Every one of the invisible corpses
had already been resurrected.
I have no idea how many or where they are.
We're surrounded, Hermes.
We have to find a way out of here now.
Survival comes first.
If we don't open the door and
escape, these'll be our last words.
I'll stretch my thread to
full extension and call FF.
For now, we back off.
You can collect the discs and
get your sweet revenge later.
I promise.
Hermes?
Right, revenge.
And that's the important part.
Jolene.
And I know it has to be equally
important to Sports Maximum,
who is hiding somewhere around here.
He wants vengeance for my
having drowned him in the pipe.
His mind must have flooded with
thoughts of how to retaliate.
He wants to chew my head to pulp,
then drain the blood spewing
from it until he's sure I'm dead.
What are you - The one who'll eventually
end me is definitely that bastard himself,
with his own foul teeth.
Don't say that!
Listen to me, Jolene.
There's tons of people who'd say getting
revenge won't bring your sister back?
as if they understand
what I'm trying to do.
And others who would tell
me forgiveness is important.
Gloria!
I don't care!
There's no way I'd force myself to forget.
That my own blood relative
was thrown into a sewer?
and just go on about my life.
This is all I've been preparing for.
Revenge is waiting.
So I can decide my own destiny
and finally satisfy it?
Hermes, can you tell me?
This isn't a standoff, right? You
can't! Get back! Don't do this!
I'm calling FF over!
There's five, no wait, seven corpses!
Breaking through the thread
and moving in on you?
Hermes, stop!
Get out of there!
Leave her alone, bitches!
Which way are you coming from?
I'm ready for you!
Shit, I'm fading fast.
Hermes!
She used a sticker to
split her head in two!
Here's my official
license to avenge. Smack!
There you are!
Sports Maximum!
How predictable you are.
I knew you'd do that.
Remember, you did the same thing when
you trapped me in that pipe before.
You used that silly sticker
that splits anything in two.
But you can see, I won't
fall for that power anymore.
Because I, too, am a corpse.
You can't kill me.
Goddamn it. That didn't work.
Where the hell is he hiding?
You're a smart girl.
Follow my voice.
What the hell?
I'll tell you.
It's your sister's fault she
witnessed an average night,
and it cost her everything she had.
Hermes, don't hurt her.
Seriously?
That's not it.
Due to that little incident, now,
after being defeated by you,
this is what I've become.
And unfortunately, my
feelings will never dissolve.
Not this one, for this one!
Listen to me.
Even if I were to suck up your
brain like jelly right now?
and fill that empty skull that's left
with the shit that's in your stomach,
my feelings of hatred towards you will
still exist throughout all of eternity,
you bitch!
It's time to say goodnight!
The one that finishes you off is me!
The moment she's been waiting for.
It's happening now.
The moment he rips off the sticker
and attempts to maul her real head.
If you peel off the sticker,
the two halves will reconjoin.
Even the piece that Sports Maxima bit
off and swallowed will fuse back in.
The jig is up!
I've ID'd your exact location.
I'm aiming right above that.
The median line of your
face, from chin to skull!
She... she did it!
One more thing.
This last parting gift is
for Gloria, you got it?
There must have been a bone in your
ugly face that got crushed before.
And I think the way that happened was
Gloria fought back hard against you.
And this...
is also for Gloria!
Whip that piece of shit
to shreds! Do it now!
What, are you gonna try to hide again?
You can't do that anymore, because I
just put a sticker on your ugly head!
and split that thing in two!
If I peel this, you'll
merge back into one!
This next one is for Gloria too!
Oh yeah, and the one after that as well.
Not to mention the next one after that.
And so on, forever!
They're all for my Gloria!
This one!
And this one!
All for Gloria!
Help, help, that.
Look, I'm finally crying.
All I want right now is to
sob my eyes out by your side.
But I don't have time or even a
speck of energy left to do it.
FF!
I need you! Heal her!
Come on, quickly!
Open this gate for me! Hurry!
Although you think I cope,
my head is filled with hope.
Of some place
other than here?
Although you think I smile!
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny.
I'm thinking
about all the
things I'd like
to do in my life.
I'm a dreamer A
distant dreamer
Dreaming far
From today
Abnormality alert activated Code
building 1A Stay right where you are!
Tell us what happened!
Don't move or you'll be a stain!
Inmate number FE40536.
Full name, Jolene Cujo!
After reading that disc, I knew...
what I need to do here.
Right now!
Thank you.